麦克斯 邮差先生来[射]了
Max, look, the mailman came.
到哪边 你胸上 还是头发上
Where am I looking, your chest, your hair?
给个提示嘛
Gimme a hint.
是这个啦 我们的驱逐令
It's here. Our eviction notice.
只需4毛6
It's amazing you can send
就能把天大耻辱送到你手 真了不起
this much shame for just 46 cents.
不是吧 半年才少交三个月租金就得走啊
What, you miss three out of six months and you're out?
打击命中率高达5成呢[棒球]
We're batting 500.
我们应该进名人堂的 好吗
That's hall of fame stuff right there.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我就顺路过来买个小蛋糕
I just stopped by to get a cupcake
在去健身房的路上吃
to eat on the way to the gym.
好 你先坐一下
Here, have a seat.
我去拿你喜欢的口味
I'll get you your usual.
麦克斯 柠檬蛋白霜小蛋糕呢
Max, where are the lemon meringue cupcakes?
不做了
Stopped making 'em.
浆果软糖味
And the fudge berries
和紫丝绒蛋糕也不做了
And the purple velvets.
我们每天都剩超多
We have so many left over every day
就连我每晚送小蛋糕给她的流浪妇女都说
that even the homeless lady I give them to at night
"小女孩 你的小店要倒了 是吧"
was like, "girl, your shop in trouble, ain't it?"
所以呢 麦克斯
So what, Max?
我们应该听从一个认为
You think we should take business advice
我国应该用麦乐鸡来当货币的
from a woman who thinks our nation's currency
流浪妇女的商业建议吗
should be the McNugget?
人家言之有理啊
She makes a good point.
现在气氛好像有点太剑拔弩张了
I think it's getting a little too real in here for me.
我要去托高我的胸 顺便粘粘我的假牙
I'm gonna go push up my boobs and glue my tooth back on.
说真的 这事我们怎么处理
Seriously, what are we gonna do about this?
我来教你怎么做吧
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
你撕烂了一封驱逐信
Aww, you ripped up an eviction notice.
这是以前我会跟我妈妈一起做的事呢
That's the one thing my mother and I used to do together.
麦克斯 我知道咱们店情况不乐观
Max, I know our shop's in trouble.
我也整天在想这问题
It's all I think about.
连我在做的春梦
Even in my sexual fantasies,
都是我在付房租给瑞恩·高斯林[帅哥男星]
I'm giving Ryan Gosling a rent check.
我只希望上天给个指示 指点我们方向
I just wish we had a sign that told us what to do.
你看 来客人了
See? Customers.
预示着我们的店不会倒
That's a sign to stay open.
给 赶紧装忙
Here, pretend to be busy.
我们会立刻给你送过去
We'll send those right out.
谢谢你的致电 奥普拉[知名女主持]
Thank you for calling, Oprah.
你好 我是乔安·莫尔斯
Hi, I'm Joanne Morse.
真希望我也能有钱到有人替我开口说话
I wish I was rich enough to have somebody talk for me.
麦克斯 你瞎啊 她是聋的
Max, are you blind? She's deaf.
好酷哦
So cool.
自从她搬进来后 我就很希望变聋子
I've wanted to be deaf ever since she moved in.
我是田纳商业地产公司的代表
I'm a representative from Tenner Commercial Real Estate.
我们想要得到您这单位
We're acquiring this property
我们愿意出钱收购你的店面
and would like to offer you a corporate buy out.
完全不懂 她说的我还比较懂呢
I understood that better when she said it.
谢谢您的邀请 但我们没有兴趣
Thank you very much, but we're not interested.
我也会一点手语
I speak a little sign language.
你刚才说的是"非常谢谢
You just said "Thank you very much,
但我现在没有穿内衣哦"
but I'm not wearing underwear."
我就知道以前的手语家教在玩我
I knew that tutor was screwing with me.
而且没穿内衣那个是我啦
And I'm the one not wearing underwear.
我们愿意出两万五的价格买下你的租约
We're ready to offer you $25,000 to take over your lease.
他奶奶的 当然好啊
Hell yes, bitch.
麦克斯 不行 你别乱说话
Max, no. What are you doing?
这小店是我们的梦想
This shop is our dream.
我们这梦想都快成恶梦了
Well, our dream is turning into a nightmare
而且没人会来唤醒我们
and no one's coming to wake us up.
这是我们的未来
This is our future.
抱歉了 真的很谢谢您 但我们不会卖的
I'm sorry, thank you very much, but we're gonna pass.
我们的生意刚开始蒸蒸日上
Our business is booming.
哎哟
Oh, yeah.
看这小伙
Look at him.
"来吧 时尚"
Come on and Vogue.
没错
Yes.
跟着音乐跳吧
Yeah, dance to the music.
还记得麦当娜还在世的那会吗
Remember when Madonna was alive?
那些年可真是美好岁月啊
Those were the good old days.
我们会给你们一点时间考虑
We'll give you some time to think about it,
不过你们拖欠租金次数过多
but with your delinquent rent history,
就算你们想留下 也得先预交六个月的租金
if you stay, we would need six months' rent up front.
我建议你们收下这两万五吧
So I'd take the $25,000.
这条件很不错了
It's a good deal.
我们会打给你 好吗
Uh, uh, we...call...you. Okay?
苏菲 这又不关你的事
Sophie, it's none of your business.
这事得我们自己决定
This is our decision.
你自己说想要上天给个指示的啊
You said you were looking for a sign.
指手划脚的手语不就是最明显的指示了吗
What's more of a sign than sign language?
不行 不必多说了
No. End of story.
就算给我全世界的"麦乐鸡"
I would not sell this shop
我也不会卖掉这小店
for all the McNuggets in the world.
我对我们的梦想还有信心
I still believe in our dream,
这梦想也绝不该在聋子中介
and it does not end with an offer
随便开个价后就轻易结束
from the deaf real estate jam.
女人啊 就爱意气用事
Women. Am I right?
厄尔 有事想你给点指教
Earl, I need some advice.
有人向我跟卡洛琳开价
Caroline and I were offered money
想收购我们小店的店面
to buy out the cupcake store,
我的守护神 "肯尼·罗杰斯"曾问过
and as my spirit animal, Kenny Rogers, once asked,
"何时该叫牌 而何时该盖牌呢"
"When do you hold 'em and when do you fold 'em?"
麦克斯 人生中有两样东西
Well, Max, there are two things in life
你必需得留下
you've got to hold on to:
"你的梦想" 以及在商店买完东西后的发票
your dreams, and your receipt when you're leaving Best Buy.
没发票的黑人绝对是茅房里提灯笼 找屎[死]啊
Oh, you do not want to be a black man without a receipt.
麦克斯 你是在故意不甩我吗
Max, did you just give me the cold shoulder?
天啊 我试着故意不甩你一年半了
Oh, my God, I've been doing that for a year and a half
你今天终于明白了
and you finally got it.
今天那么甩头就走是我不对
I'm sorry for storming out earlier,
但我们不能这么轻易放弃
but we just can't give it up that easy.
我能 也有过 也会继续这么做
I can, and have, and will again.
我们现在抽身 说不定是明智之举呢
Maybe it's better if we just get out now.
我听到一个顾客在说
I heard a customer saying
全食超市要在附近开新店面呢
a Whole Foods is going in over there.
你知道什么人会去那里买东西吗
You know who goes to Whole Foods?
穿着怪胎五指鞋的有钱妇女
Rich ladies with those freaky toe sneakers.
老娘绝对不想看见穿怪胎五指鞋的人
And I cannot be seeing no freaky toe sneakers.
全食超市吗
Whole Foods?
这就是我想看到的老天爷指示啊
That's the sign I've been looking for.
难怪他们想赶我们走呢
No wonder they wanted to get rid of us.
全食超市一开
With a whole foods there,
他们就能合理涨租金
they can raise everybody's rent.
没差啊 反正我们又不付
That's fine, we don't pay it anyway.
我就知道这里会成为炙手可热的新区
I knew it was gonna be the hot new neighborhood.
被我料中了 能行了 麦克斯
I knew it! This is it, Max.
全食超市一进驻 基佬们就会跟着来
First comes the Whole Foods, then come the gays,
然后明星也会过来
then the celebrities.
我们附近有公园
Well, the gays will come anyway
本来就能吸引一大堆基佬
as long as there's a park.
麦克斯 说真的 成功只是早晚的问题
Seriously, Max, it's just a matter of time
我们很快就有机会对安妮·海瑟薇说
before we're telling Anne Hathaway,
"你的假笑不管用
"Forget that fake smile
想买小蛋糕就跟大家一样乖乖排队"
and just go wait in line like everybody else."
阿憨 我们小蛋糕店附近
Han, they're opening up a whole Foods
要开一家全食超市呢
right near our cupcake shop.
又一家全食超市啊
Another Whole Foods?
是不是要等"全食"变"全国"他们才满意啊
They won't be happy till it's "Whole Country," am I right?
我在网上个帖子里看到的
I saw that on a meme.
当务之急是要守住这家宝店
Now we have to stay in that neighborhood.
我们只要想出去哪筹六个月的租金就行了
We just have to come up with six months rent up front.
女孩们 我很乐意伸出援手
Well, I'd love to help you, ladies,
但我在2008年 就忘了我银行卡的密码
but I forgot my pin number in 2008.
等等 2008
Wait a minute, 2008.
那就是我的密码
That's my pin number!
你们想跟我借啊
You want my money?
偶的天啊
Ehr mah gerd.
我最近在网上看了很多热帖
I've been looking at a lot of memes.
我想起来你长得像谁了
Oh, that's who you look like.
暴躁猫
Grumpy cat!
麦克斯 我知道我们能借的都借了
Max, I know we've borrowed from everyone we know,
但我非常确定这条路是对的
but I'm so convinced that this is the right thing
我愿意牺牲去做一件
that I'm willing to stoop to something
我永远也不会做的事
I never thought I'd do.
你的确是很甜美又可爱
Look, you're sweet and you're adorable,
但是你太骨感了 一个晚上顶多只能"赚"到40
but you're way too bony to bring in more than 40 a night.
就算你有只动物做噱头搭档
And even if you got an animal sidekick,
我们还是到不了那目标
it's still not gonna get us there.
但是够我"到"了
It would get me there.
我们可以预约一下 去市中心
We can make an appointment, go into the city,
然后跟我查莉蒂姑姑借钱
and ask my Aunt Charity for the money.
她是化妆品王国的总裁
She's president of a cosmetic empire
富得流油
and she's filthy rich.
那为什么你什么屁话都说
And how is she literally the only thing
却从没提起过她啊
you've never talked about?
因为她很讨厌我啊
Because she hates me.
亲人就是这样啊
That's what family is.
亲人就是恨你 但又不能杀你的人
People who hate you, but can't kill you
因为你死了 警察会第一个找他们问话
'cause they're the first ones questioned.
真没想到你们还在等
I'm surprised you're still waiting.
大多数人等两个小时就走人了
Most people leave after two hours.
没事 我们能等
Well, it's not a problem for us.
要我们等两小时 三小时 一天都没问题
We'll wait two hours, three, a whole day.
等一天估计差不多了
That sounds about right.
-斯蒂芬妮 -来了
- Stephanie. - Coming.
我不叫这名字
That's not my name,
但是我不敢纠正她
but I'm afraid to tell her.
你姑姑为什么不喜欢你啊
So why doesn't your aunt like you?
不知道 她就不喜欢我啊
I don't know. She just doesn't like me.
还记得我十岁那年 有一次
For example, one time, when I was ten,
我跟她在我家的海边度假别墅里
and we were at our Hamptons beach house--
我已经不喜欢你了
I already don't like you.
我想用我的海鸥杯喝我的晚安热可可
I wanted my night-night cocoa in my special seagull mug--
现在我恨你了
Now I hate you.
查莉蒂姑姑是我当时的保姆
And my Aunt Charity, who was babysitting
因为其他人都去欧洲
because everybody else was in Europe
参加马术比赛了
at the dressage competition...
现在我想把你打得半死不活 再留你自生自灭
Now I've beat you up and left you for dead.
她说我的海鸥杯摔烂了
Told me my seagull cup was broken
但我知道杯子肯定没烂
and I knew it wasn't.
然后我就一直哭个不停
And when I wouldn't stop crying,
她就把我锁在我房间里
she locked me in my bedroom,
然后趁佣人们不注意的时候
and when the servants weren't looking,
还扯我头发
pulled my hair.
偶像啊
Love her.
你们可以进去了
You can go in now.
哪这么大事啊 凯文
It's not that big a deal, Kevin.
对目标消费者发行唇膏而已
We're launching a lipstick at target,
又不是对伊朗发射飞弹
not a missile at Iran.
你好啊 查莉蒂姑姑
Aunt Charity, hi.
卡洛琳 你瞧你
Caroline, look at you.
明艳动人 亭亭玉立
Gorgeous, beautiful.
也没嫌弃你那鼻子 保持了下来 挺好的
You stuck with that nose. Good for you.
这位有性感双唇的美女是谁呢
And who's this with the great lips?
查莉蒂姑姑 她是我的好朋友
Aunt Charity, this is my friend
与生意伙伴 麦克斯
and business partner, Max.
幸会幸会
Nice to meet you.
她是不是跟你说了我扯她头发的事
Did she tell you I pulled her hair?
那是我们家族里的一桩悬案
Oh, it was legend around the family townhouse.
我哥还为此走进我的房间
My brother came into my room.
"你是不是扯了我小公主的头发
"Did you pull my princess's hair?
她说你扯了她头发"
She said you pulled her hair."
拜托哦 她当时10岁 我23岁了
I mean, come on. She's 10, I'm 23.
我怎么会没事伸手去拉她头发啊
What, I'm just gonna reach up and pull her hair?
那怎么可能呢
I mean, how would that happen?
怎么会有人没事去拉一个小孩的头发啊
I mean, who would just pull a child's hair?
你说吧 我会没事去拉她头发吗
I mean, come on. I'm gonna pull her hair?
拉她头发吗
Pull her hair?
扯她头发咩
你刚就扯了我头发
Okay, you just pulled my hair.
老天啊 旧事又重演了
Oh my God, here we go again.
赶紧找好律师
Get the lawyers.
来吧 请坐
Come on, have a seat.
就坐这大女孩椅子上吧
Have a seat in the big girl chair.
你现在是大女孩了
You're a big girl now.
查莉蒂姑姑 谢谢你抽空见我们
Aunt Charity, thank you so much for seeing us.
我知道你的时间超级宝贵
I know your time is very valuable.
我的所有时间都愿意保留给你
I have all the time in the world for you.
你是家人嘛
You're family.
斯蒂芬妮 我现在什么要紧事要干
Stephanie, I'm not doing anything important.
把文件拿进来给我签名吧
Bring me those documents to sign.
我25岁以后就没见过她了
I haven't seen this one since I was 25
当年我被我父母切断金援
and my parents cut me off.
因为我跟个巴基斯坦籍拉拉"睡"
You sleep with one Pakistani lesbian,
结果就被踢出家族了
You're out of the family.
给 大唇妞 试试这些
Here, you with the big lips, try these.
告诉我你最讨厌哪一个
Tell me which ones you hate.
查莉蒂姑姑在她26岁的时候创了业
Aunt Charity started her makeup empire at 26
当时她发明了泡泡糖口味的唇蜜
when she invented bubblegum-flavored lip gloss.
天啊 那是你发明的啊
Oh my God, that was you?
我爱死那个了
I loved that.
我初吻时 就擦了那个
I was wearing that during my first kiss.
谢谢你 那个吻让我们老师给我个"A"
And thank you, because I got an "A" in that class.
每个爱唇膏的女孩都爱我
Every girl who loves lipstick loves me,
除了这丫头之外 她恨死我了
except for this one, who hates me
因为我欺负她
because I was so mean
还打破了她的晚安可可杯
and I broke her night-night cocoa cup.
查莉蒂姑姑 我从没说你欺负我啊
Aunt Charity, I never said you were mean.
我当时才10岁 而且我也只是对
I was ten, and I just got a little confused
我海鸥杯的下落有点疑惑嘛
about what happened to my seagull cup.
但我现在长大了
But I'm an adult now.
我去睡觉的时候
When I go night-night,
不会再想那个可可杯了
I barely even think about that cocoa cup.
卡洛琳 我当时才23岁
Caroline, I was 23.
我根本不记得什么杯子
I don't remember anything about a cup.
我只记得那个周末
All I remember about that weekend
著名设计师范思哲被人谋杀了
was that Versace was murdered
我的裙子送到我手肯定已经过时了
and my dress would obviously be late.
为什么你会来呢
Now, why are you here?
告诉我吧 我会全神贯注听你说
Tell me. You have my full and undivided attention.
签哪里
Where and where?
查莉蒂姑姑 不知道你是否知道
Well, Aunt Charity, as you may or may not know,
我现在处于创业阶段
I now have a start-up business.
是我 还是这看起来真的像狗的鸡鸡
Hey, is it me, or does this look like a dog penis?
她真幽默 看起来很专业
She's fun. Seems professional.
好眼光
Good choice.
如你所知
And, as you know,
我向来敬仰你的商业才能
I've always respected your business acumen.
-即使在我小时候... -要多少
- Even when I was a little... - How much?
好 咱们就打开天窗说亮话
Fine, businesswoman to businesswoman--
我要个数目 给我个数目
I need a number. Give me a number.
以及所有这些唇膏
And all these lipsticks,
包括那根狗狗的鸡鸡
including dog penis.
我不是让你白给我
And I'm not asking for a handout.
-这是个让你入股的商机 -不要
- This is a business opportunity. - No.
或许值得考虑 还是算了
Maybe--no.
卡洛琳
Look, Caroline,
如果这真的是商业交易
if this were truly a business transaction,
你会带着你的小蛋糕来见我 可你没有
you'd have cupcakes here to show me, but you don't.
我知道你在搞什么生意
I know all about your business.
斯蒂芬妮上网搜过你
Stephanie googled you.
她还有力气打开网页搜索我们啊
She has the strength to google?
那她有搜索过"如何进食"吗
Has she googled "how to eat"?
慢走不送
See yourselves out.
我约了我的皮肤科医师做点小手术
I'm going to my dermatologist for a little procedure.
我想让自己看上去年轻两岁
I want to take two years off my face
好让人们在心里猜
just so people will think,
"她是38岁 还是39岁啊
"Is she 38 or 39?
太难判断了"
It's so hard to tell."
可我想告诉你 你是我保住梦想
But just so you know, you were my last chance
和我们蛋糕店的最后希望
to keep my dream and our business alive.
你足智多谋 会想到别的办法的
You're resourceful. You'll think of something.
现在给我过来
Now come here.
尽管如此 我们还是一家人
In spite of it all, we are family.
给我个拥抱
Give me a hug.
她简直是个女魔头
She's kind of a monster,
但她白送我东西 我好为难呀
but she gave me free stuff, so I'm torn.
查莉蒂姑姑是个有头脑的商业女性
Aunt Charity's a smart businesswoman.
她不会随便否决一个好产品
She won't be able to deny a good product.
真不敢相信我居然帮你做蛋糕
I can't believe I'm making cupcakes
好让你回去跟那个女人大战第二个回合
so you can go back for round two with that woman.
你的查莉蒂姑姑绝非善类啊
Auntie Charity might be the anti-christ.
为了让我们的店撑下去 我豁出去了
I'll do anything to keep our business going.
如果这些小蛋糕不管用
And if these cupcakes don't work,
我们就告诉她 你是巴基斯坦人
we'll tell her you're Pakistani
让她扑你
and let her go after it.
就算你说服她给我们钱
Even if you do convince her to give us the money,
那也是求来的脏钱
that's bitch money.
我们不要求来的脏钱
We don't take bitch money.
麦克斯 你还在别人尿尿的地方捡一分钱硬币呢
Max, you pick up pennies off the pee corner.
才没有 那是十分钱 好吗
Not true. Dimes and up.
-你好 我们很快就走 -不行不行
- Hi! We'll just be a second. - Oh, no. Oh, no.
发型不错 大卫·鲍威
Cool hair, David Bowie.
她今天不想见任何人
Okay, she's definitely not seeing anyone today.
抱歉闯了进来 查莉蒂姑姑
Sorry to burst in, Aunt Charity,
但我们想你试试我们的小蛋糕
but we wanted you to have some of our cupcakes.
想年轻两岁就得削两层皮
It took two layers to take off two years,
但这是值得的
but it was worth it.
告诉你们 第三层就是骨头了
Just so you know, the third layer is bone.
我要么是嗨了 要么就是我的椅子融化了
Either I'm high, or my chair melted.
好吧 你是晕乎了
Okay, you're high.
为了止痛 她在吃吗啡棒棒糖
She's on morphine lollipops for the pain.
真的吗 我愿意为了乐趣吃一根
Really? 'Cause I'd like to be on one for the fun.
我感觉很棒棒棒 *
* I got that boom boom boom
到时间帮你换面膜了
Okay, it's time to change your face mask.
不如让我来吧
You know what? Let me do that.
我可以帮查莉蒂姑姑的忙
I can help my Aunt Charity.
我愿意帮家族里的任何人做任何事
I'll do anything to help someone in my family
因为家人就是要相互帮助
because families help each other.
那你何不帮自己个忙
Well, why don't you help yourself
去做一对成年人大小的咪咪
to an adult-sized pair of boobies?
我喜欢我的胸部 也喜欢我的鼻子
Like my boobs, like my nose.
这是新的面膜
Okay, here's the new face mask.
你把脏的那块揭下来
you peel the soiled one off,
然后用棉签擦拭手术区
then swab the affected area with q-tips.
我离开模特界
And I left modeling
是因为我觉得那不够体面
because I thought it was degrading.
-问你个问题 斯蒂芬妮 -什么
- Question, Stephanie. - Yeah?
棒棒糖有甜橙或酸橙口味的吗
Do these come in orange, or lime,
还是光就这一种口味
or is it just the white flavor?
算了
Ah, screw it.
再舔两下 啥味的都无所谓了
After a couple of licks, it won't matter.
我很乐意帮你换面膜 查莉蒂姑姑
I'm happy to do this for you, Aunt Charity,
不仅仅是为了钱 还因为我们是家人
And not just for the money, but 'cause we're family.
我讨厌你
I hate you.
一直都讨厌你
Always have.
这不是真心话吧 查莉蒂姑姑
You can't mean that, Aunt Charity.
在你出生前 我曾是家里的小公主
Up until you were born, I was the family princess.
你出生后 所有人都觉得你"棒棒棒"
And then you came in, and you got the boom boom boom.
你抢走了我的"棒棒棒"
And you took my boom boom boom.
所以我把你锁进房间间间
So I locked you in a room room room.
抱歉让你觉得 是我抢走了你的"棒棒棒"
Well, I'm sorry you think I took your boom boom boom,
但你真的拿走了我的海鸥杯
but you really did take my seagull cup
还把我锁进房间
and lock me in a room.
间间
Room room.
我可不会给你一分钱的 小姑娘
I'm not giving you any money, little girl.
我丑话说在先
Just so you know.
或许你尝过我们的小蛋糕后
Well, maybe you'll feel differently
你会改变你的想法
after you taste one of our cupcakes.
来 我们何不花时间尝一口
Here, why don't we take a minute for a little bite?
不 我不想吃
Nope, I don't want it.
它会让你知道 投资我们绝对错不了
It'll show you what a good business investment we are.
来 吃一口 过来
Here, come--come here.
就尝一口嘛
Just--oh--just taste it.
来
Here.
拜托 尝尝 吃一口
Come on, taste-take a bite.
这场面真让人不舒服
This is pretty disturbing.
如果我现在不是爽翻天
I would intervene right now
我早过去阻止你了
if I wasn't feeling amazing.
很好吃 对吧
Yummy, right?
不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
不要啊 那是你的脸
No, no, no, that's your face.
我觉得你嚼的是你的脸皮
I think you're chewing your face.
那是我吃过最好吃的小蛋糕
That's the best cupcake I have ever had,
但我还是不会给你一分钱的
But I am still not giving you any money.
为什么 这是你摔烂我的海鸥杯后
Why not? It's the least you could do
唯一能补偿我的机会
after you broke my seagull cup.
天啊 你还要提你那个海鸥杯吗
Oh, my god, are you still talking about that seagull cup?
我都15年没想到它了
I haven't thought about that in 15 years.
如果我们要讨论那个白痴海鸥杯
If we're gonna be talking about that stupid seagull cup,
那我得再吃一根棒棒糖
I'm gonna need another lollipop.
她把糖放哪里了
Where does she keep them?
这里 装在一个有海鸥的杯子里
Oh, here, they're in this cup that has a seagull on it.
慢着
Wait.
我之前在哪里听说过海鸥杯来着
Where have I heard of seagull cup before?
那是我的晚安可可杯
That's my night-night cocoa cup.
我就知道它没有摔烂
I knew it wasn't broken.
你居然偷偷藏了这么多年
You hid it and kept it all these years?
你奈我何
Yep.
为什么你要这样伤害我
Why would you want to hurt me like that?
还不够明显吗
It's obvious.
她迷恋自己的哥哥
She's obsessed with her brother,
她把你的出生视为
and she saw your being born
抢走她哥哥所有的爱
as his love being taken away from her.
靠 这玩意让老娘一秒钟变聪明
Damn, this thing makes me smart.
希望你现在开心了
Well, I hope you're happy now,
因为我失去的不只是这个晚安可可杯
because I lost a lot more than my night-night cocoa cup.
我失去我的家产 我的父亲
I lost my money, my father,
现在我还即将失去我的梦想
and now I'm about to lose my dream.
告诉你 我们走人了
And you know what? We're done.
你想得美 才不走
You know what? We are not done.
我不是个轻易放弃的人
I am not a quitter.
我说过会帮你把面膜贴上
I said I would put your new face on,
所以没做到我决不离开
so I'm not leaving here until I do.
她的脸没了
Her face is gone.
她简直就是钱宁家的《歌剧魅影》
She's basically the phantom of the Channing.
好了 这样应该差不多了
All right, that's close enough.
别再说我是被宠坏的孩子
And stop calling me spoiled.
自从我失去了一切 我努力工作
Since I lost it all, I've worked hard.
我打扫过厕所 打死过老鼠
I've cleaned toilets, I've killed rats,
我为了成功 什么都愿意做
I've done everything I had to to be a success.
告诉她 麦克斯
Tell her, Max.
我感觉很棒棒棒 *
* I got that boom boom boom
-我感觉很棒... -算了 我们走
- I got that boom- - Okay, fine. Let's go.
站住
Stop.
好 我会给你钱
Fine, I'll give you the money.
不是因为你是我的侄女
Not--not just because you're my niece,
而是因为你强迫自己来这里
but because you forced yourself in here
像一个强卖的女商人 我是指
like a pushy businesswoman, which is--
你把蛋糕硬塞进我喉咙[硬要我接受]
you shoved your cupcake down my throat.
因为换做是我 我也会做同样的事
That is exactly what I would have done.
签名 查莉蒂·钱...
Signed Char-ity Chan...
天啊
Oh, no.
查莉蒂姑姑 你还好吧
Aunt Charity, are you all right?
她没有签完她的名字
Oh, and she didn't finish signing it.
不过那也是我的姓 那就我代劳吧
Well, it's my last name too, so...
宁
Ing.
她的头压住了 我拿不出来
I can't get it out from under her head.
扯她的头发 你报仇的机会来了
Pull her hair! Now's your chance.
鲍勃 我觉得你没有表达清
Bob, I don't feel you are getting across
我的愤怒之情 我自己比手语吧
my passion about this, so I'll just sign it.
那张支票应该能兑现的
That check should have cleared.
你刚才的手语是说 "你的脸长得像屁股"
That time, you said, "Your face looks like a butt."
我很欣赏你们为了继续经营而做出的努力
I appreciate how hard you've tried to stay in business,
但好汉不吃眼前亏
but do the smart thing.
收下这笔钱 重新开始
Take the money. Start fresh.
你们只需签了这份合同
All you have to do is sign this.
我们俩需要时间讨论
Well, we will have to discuss it.
-我的搭档对此... -快签
- My partner has a be- - Just sign it.
讨论完毕
Good discussion.
卡洛琳·钱
Caroline Chan--
麦克斯 帮帮我
Max, a little help.
宁
Ing.
从这一刻开始
So, as of this moment,
这里不再是麦克斯自制小蛋糕店了
this space is no longer Max's homemade cupcakes.
恭喜你们 也祝你们好运
Congratulations and good luck.
乔安和那个聋女人愉快地走了
Well, there goes Joanne and that deaf lady.
这箭头我们要拿走
We are keeping the arrow.
真不敢相信我姑姑会不兑现那张支票
I can't believe my aunt would stop payment on that check.
而且干这种事后 她居然还有脸来
And I can't believe she'd show up here after she did.
查莉蒂姑姑
Aunt Charity, do you know
你知道我现在怎么想你吗
what I'm thinking about you right now?
想什么 我像38岁还是39岁吗
What? I look 38 or 39,
难以判断吧
it's hard to tell?
别表现得那么受伤嘛
Oh, don't look so wounded.
你知道我必须取消那张支票
You know I had to stop that check.
你居然占一个神志不清的人的便宜
You took advantage of someone in a morphine haze.
如果你觉得那就是占你便宜
If you think that was being taken advantage of,
那你肯定没有在学校誓师大会上晕倒过
you've never blacked out at a pep rally.
没错 我是取消了那张支票 但这个给你
Yes, I stopped that check, but here.
这似乎对你很重要
This seems important to you.
以前是
Seemed.
那时我还是无忧无虑的富家女
Seemed when I was rich.
而现在 我有实际问题要解决
Now I have real problems.
就是 里面的棒棒糖呢
Yeah, and where are them lollipops at?
-你剥夺了我的未来 -还有我的棒棒糖
- You took away my future. - And my lollipops.
不 卡洛琳 我剥夺的只是我的钱
No, Caroline, I took away my money.
通过强迫你自己寻找出路
And by forcing you to find you own way,
我可能会还给你一个更好的将来
I may have given you a better future.
店挺可爱
Cute shop.
但店面太大 开得太早
Too big, too soon.
你总有一天会明白的
You'll figure it out.
查莉蒂姑姑
Aunt Charity?
你看起来像42岁
You look 42.
我们都知道我不像
We all know I don't.
蛋糕店没了
The shop's over.
我以前还坚信我们会成功
Wow, I thought for sure we'd be a success.
谁说我们不是呢
Well, who says we're not?
开这店也有过不少开心事啊
I mean, we had some fun, right?
我们还有了这个超酷的红箭头
And we have a cool-ass red arrow.
我们有这么多钱
And we have this big check,
足够拿来还给苏菲
which is just enough to pay back Sophie
和其他借钱给我们的人
and everybody else we owe money to.
那倒是
That's true.
所以我们也算是成功还清债务吧
So in a way, we're kind of success.
我们从身无分文到收支平衡
I mean, we did go from broke to broke even.
我们成功了
We nailed it.
我真希望老天能给个明确的指示
I just wish we had a clear-cut sign
告诉我们放弃这里是明智的
that letting go of this place was the right thing to do.
偶的天
Ehr mah gerd!
我的晚安可可杯
My night-night cocoa cup.
你要指示是吗 这就是你要的指示
You wanted a sign? That's your sign!
不管碰到什么灾难 你都能安然无恙
No matter what hits you, you'll be okay.
突然觉得买下这里的人好可怜呀
Well, I feel sorry for whoever owns this dump.